m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：淫贼叫兽赛太公  受骗学生YY猫  猫中之王  醉芝士
校对：淫贼叫兽赛太公  受骗学生YY猫总监   YY猫
后期：孤帆   时间轴：YY猫
生活大爆炸
第七季  第七集
我从没见过他这么欢乐
I've never seen him this happy before.
那是因为你从来没有在
That's because you've never seen him
"医药箱补货日"见过他
on "Restock the Medicine Cabinet Day."
你们看
Look!
新出的带麻药局部抗组胺剂呢
A new topical antihistamine with lidocaine.
好想赶快发疹子来用用看啊
I can't wait until I get a rash.
解胀气药也出了加强版呢
Oh, Gas-X has a new ultra strength.
看来他们真会看顾客意见邮箱啊
I guess they really do read their mail.
那不是质子教授吗
Hey, isn't that Professor Proton?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你们看他  像普通人一样排队
Look at him, just standing in line
好像自己30年前并不是个二流名人似地
like he wasn't moderately famous 30 years ago.
去跟他打招呼吧
Let's go say hello.
我们还是别烦人家比较好吧
Oh, maybe we shouldn't bother him.
我没有要去烦他啊  我是要去跟他聊聊
I'm not going to bother him, I'm going to talk to him.
他总以为这两者不一样
He thinks there's a difference.
亚瑟
Arthur?
亚瑟  是我啊
Arthur, it's me--
谢尔顿・库珀
Sheldon Cooper.
你可能因为年事已高忘了我是谁了
You may not remember because of your advanced age.
相信我  你化成灰我也认得
Trust me, I... I remember.
这位是我的女朋友  艾米
This is my girlfriend, Amy.
艾米  这位是电视圈传奇亚瑟・杰弗里斯
Amy, this is television legend Arthur Jeffries.
他的科普节目启发了无数孩子
His science show inspired millions of children.
等  等等
Ho-hold on.
你...  你有女朋友啊
You... You have a girlfriend?
是的  久仰大名啊
Yes, and I've heard so much about you.
而且你看  我们穿着同款矫正鞋呢
Hey look-- we're wearing the same orthopedic shoes.
真不敢相信我跟名人穿同样的鞋
I can't believe I dress like a celebrity.
现在我明白了
O-Okay, I get it now.
你好  我是莱纳德・霍夫斯塔德
Dr. Jeffries, hello again. Leonard Hofstadter.
是你啊  我记得你的女朋友
Oh, oh, right, I remember your-your girlfriend.
她...  她在吗
Is-Is she... is she here?
她不在这里
No, she's not.
你是来补什么药的存货呢
So, what prescription are you getting filled?
-谢尔顿  -别说  让我猜猜
- Sheldon. - Wait, I want to guess.
别告诉我答案
Don't tell me.
我本来就没打算告诉你
I wasn't going to tell you.
谢尔顿  别玩了
Sheldon, come on.
不不不  玩这个我最拿手了
No, no, no. I'm really good at this.
好  给我的提示
All right, give me a hint.
是不是跟排某些液体有困难有关
Does it involve difficulty initiating a stream of anything?
看我的年纪就知道  猜中很容易吧
Well, given my age, that's more than just a lucky guess.
谢尔顿  我们还是去取笑
Hey, Sheldon, let's go mock the people
买顺势疗法药的人吧  你不是很喜欢吗
buying homeopathic medicine-- you love that.
但是我现在跟朋友一起
But I'm hanging out with my friend,
我们聊得正欢呢
and we're having fun.
你看他多开心
Look how happy he is.
妮妮这周五要在家里办闺蜜之夜
Bernie's having a girls' night on Friday at our place.
不如那晚咱俩出去玩呀
You want to do something?
-那晚我有事呢  -什么事
- Actually, I'm busy. - Doing what?
科罗拉多大街那边开了一家新体育酒吧...
There's a new sports bar over on Colorado Ave...
-你也要去参加闺蜜之夜  -是啦
- You're going to girls' night. - Yeah.
你知道她们是要串珠宝的对吧
You know they're making jewelry, right?
你以为那主意是她们想出来的吗
You think they came up with that?
她们本来是要喝啤酒  射飞镖好吗
They were going to drink beer and play darts.
怎么样啦[什么上升]
What's up?
绝对不是他的睾丸酮水平
Not his testosterone levels.
别乱说
Excuse me.
人家对自己的男子气概很满意好咩
I happen to be very comfortable with my masculinity.
这怎么可能
How is that possible?
质子教授给我发了电邮
Hey, I got an email from Professor Proton.
好耶  他说什么了
Goody! What's it say?
他在写一篇纳米真空管的论文
He's working on a paper about nano vacuum tubes,
问我能不能帮他看看
and wants to know if I'd take a look at it.
奇怪
That's strange.
他居然会找你  而不是找我帮忙
That he would come to you for that and not me.
我收到他两封电邮呢
Oh, I got two emails from him.
"你有莱纳德的邮箱吗"
"Do you have Leonard's email address?"
还有
And...
"不用了  我找到了"
"Never mind, I found it."
他居然会选你不选我
I can't believe he picked you over me.
你也不会想看一篇好几十年没正经
You don't want to read a paper by some old has-been
搞过科研的过气老头写的论文呢
who hasn't done any real science in decades.
这有什么好哭诉的
Yeah, it's nothing to cry about.
谢尔顿・库伯才不哭呢
Sheldon Cooper does not cry.
有道理  你个机器人碰水会生锈
It's true, you'd rust.
想到我居然曾经当他是我偶像
And to think I idolized that man.
我何苦呢
And why?
说到底  他不过也是个好莱坞伪君子罢了
At the end of the day he's just another Hollywood phony.
这事情真的值得你不开心吗
Is it really worth getting upset about?
常言道  别见你心中的英雄
They say don't meet your heroes.
不要窥探他们名望与名声背后的真实
Don't peek behind that curtain of fame and celebrity,
如果你犯了这禁忌  你会看到真实的他们
because if you do, you'll see them as they really are--
堕落的卖笑戏子
degenerate carnival folk.
别这样  他只是个退休的儿童节目主持
Come on, he's a retired kids show host.
这才更糟呢
That's even worse.
用美好的科学当糖果
Using the sweet candy of science
骗取小孩对他的爱慕
to trick children into loving him.
死淫贼
Pervert.
你有仔细想过
Have you ever thought about
为什么亚瑟没找你读论文吗
why Arthur didn't want you to read his paper?
我想过
Yes, I have.
我唯一的结论就是
And my only conclusion
他那天在药房买的药
is the prescription he was picking up the other day
是要治神经病的
was for cuckoo pills.
有可能是他觉得你有点过了吧
Maybe he found you, um, a bit much.
你这话说得才过吧
That's kind of a stretch.
要说社交技巧
Look, when it comes to social skills,
我已经掌握了三大技巧
I've mastered the big three.
首先是腼腆一笑
There's the coy smile.
以及友善的轻笑
There's the friendly chuckle.
以及如何发出同情音
There's the vocalization of sympathy.
最后这个太难了  我还在练
That last one's tricky, I'm still working on it.
就我那天看到的情况来看
From what I saw the other day,
我能理解他或...
I could understand why he and...
有些人可能会觉得你
some people might find you...
什么
What?
算了
Doesn't matter.
不行  快说
No, go ahead, say it.
我知道你想说什么
I know what it is.
我这辈子听过无数遍了
I've heard it my whole life.
你想说的是"惹人厌"
The word's "annoying".
说吧  说吧
Go ahead, say it.
快说  说我惹人厌
Say it. Say I'm annoying.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
我才不会觉得受伤
Oh, it won't hurt my feelings.
说吧  艾米  说我惹人厌啊
Go ahead, Amy, say I'm annoying.
我惹人厌  我超级惹人厌
I'm annoying. I'm annoying.
我最惹人厌了  没错
I'm annoying. Yeah, now, uh...
你要去哪里
Now where are you going?
你知道你想说出口  快说啊
Look, you know you want to say it-- say it.
说我惹人厌  快说啊
Say I'm annoying. Go ahead, say it.
说啊  艾米  快说啊
Say it. Say it. Amy, say it.
这妞不能忍受我是对的就走啊
Well, she can't stand it when I'm right.
真有意思
This is fun.
我会像戴着珠宝的那种傲娇的贵妇
I'm going to feel like such a vixen wearing jewelry
只不过我不会对一大堆药物过敏
that doesn't have a list of medications I'm allergic to.
佩妮  你做得怎么样
Penny, how's it going over there?
很好  只是我有点搞不定胶水
Good-- I'm just having little trouble with the glue.
你难道不会用胶水吗
How do you not know how to use glue?
你学前班老逃课了吧
Did you ditch pre-school?
是啊  当时我忙着跟二年级的学生约会呢
Yeah, but only because I was dating a second grader.
各位好啊
Hello, everyone.
好吧  你想说什么就说吧
Okay, let me have it.
你只管开"拉杰是娘们"的玩笑好了
Let's hear all the "Raj is a girl" jokes.
你想错了
Nope.
伯纳黛特说这样不对  她不许我这样
Bernadette told me it isn't nice and I'm not allowed.
那还真是多谢了
Thank you.
所以我不会嘲笑你
So I won't be making fun of you,
也不会耻笑你喜欢的事物
or the things you like,
更不会讥笑你"只想玩乐"的事实
or the fact that you just want to have fun.
源自辛迪・劳帕的著名单曲《Girls Just Wanna Have Fun 女孩们只想玩乐》
华仔  别说了
Howie, stop.
过来看看我做的东西
Come on, look at what I'm making.
还挺好看的嘛
Oh, that's actually pretty nice.
我在做手镯
I'm making a bracelet.
而我做的是"一团糟"
Yeah, I'm just making a mess.
你们其实可以拿我的焊铁玩
You know, instead of beads and glue,
而不是在这光玩珠子和胶水
you guys can use my soldering iron.
这样你们可以做更酷的东西
You'd be able to make much cooler stuff.
我觉得这样就挺好  谢啦
Oh, I think we're doing just fine, thank you.
-老实说  我想试试  -我也是
- Actually, I'd kind of like to try that. - Me, too.
马上给你们拿来
Be right back.
我胳膊上怎么黏有开心果
When did I have pistachios?
亚瑟
Arthur.
门环
Door knocker.
从那个电视节目赚的吧
That's TV money.
同名DIY电视节目
谢尔顿  你来这儿干嘛
Sheldon, what are you doing here?
抱歉  我吵醒你了吗
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
当然啦  现在都晚上7点半了
Of course you woke me, it's 7:30.
本来我可以早点到的
Well, I would have been here sooner,
但不知道为什么
but for some reason your home
你家不在"好莱坞明星之家"这幅地图上
isn't on this map of Hollywood stars.
你找我有事吗  谢尔顿
What do you want, Sheldon?
我的女朋友指出
It's been pointed out by my girlfriend
那天我可能惹到你了
that I may have been annoying to you.
这么懂事的姑娘你可别放手
She sounds like a keeper.
总之我想跟你道歉
Anyway, I wanted to apologize.
真的很对不起
I am truly sorry.
好的  我接受你的道歉  晚安
All right, apology accepted. Have a nice night.
不  还有呢  既然我们冰释前嫌
No, no, now that... we've cleared the air,
我还想跟你商量一件事
I wanted to discuss another matter with you.
谢尔顿  再过两个小时  我就得起床
Sheldon, in a couple hours, I have to get up,
尿个尿  然后在房子里游荡[梦游]
pee and then wander around the house.
那我长话短说
Well, then, I'll make this quick.
我想跟你谈谈你发给莱纳德那篇论文
Um, I want to talk about the paper you sent Leonard.
我知道他说可行性很高
Now, I know he said it's promising
他也打算跟你合作
and he's going to collaborate on it,
但现在我们又是朋友了
but now that you and I are friends again,
我随时听候您差遣
I am at your disposal.
坦白说  借助我的名字和声望会对论文大有帮助
Frankly, lending my name and reputation to it will help,
因为很多人都认为你已经是"过气的前浪"
because a lot of people think that you're a washed-up has-been.
或已经"死在沙滩上"了
Or dead.
那我真是走了大运啊
I should be so lucky.
那你觉得怎么样
So, uh, what do you say?
如果你还是跟以前一样
You know, if it's all the same with you,
那我还是继续跟莱纳德合作吧
I think I'll stick with Leonard.
因为我惹人厌  对吧
It's because I'm annoying, right?
我知道  说啊
I know it is. Say it.
快说  说我惹人厌
Say it. Say I'm annoying.
-晚安  -说啊
- Good night. - Say it.
亚瑟  说啊  说我惹人厌
Arthur, say it. Say I'm annoying.
说啊  快说啊
Say it. Say it.
说我惹人厌
I'm annoying. Say it.
你超级惹人厌
You're annoying!
人家好伤心啊
Wow, that really hurt.
如果在我小时候  有人跟我说
If you would have told me when I was a kid
我长大后会有机会
that someday I would be doing science
跟质子教授一起做实验
next to Professor Proton,
我一定不会相信
I would not have believed you.
如果有人跟我说
If someone had told me
人们在我83岁的时候
that people would still call me Professor Proton
还会称我为"质子教授"
when I was 83 years old,
我肯定不会戒烟
I never would have quit smoking.
抱歉  杰弗里斯博士  我只是太兴奋了
I'm sorry, Dr. Jeffries, I'm just excited.
你对于纳米真空管的想法很有意思
This nano vacuum tube idea of yours is really interesting.
你好啊  莱纳德
Hello, Leonard.
你好  亚瑟
Oh, hello, Arthur.
你们俩都在这里  真是意外的巧合呀
What an odd coincidence that you're both here.
有什么巧合的
Why is it odd?
因为碰巧的是  我今天也跟一位
Because as it just so happens, I'm also spending the day
深受儿童喜爱的电视科学明星在一起
with a beloved children's television science personality.
对不对呀  我的新友兼新同事
Isn't that right, new friend and colleague,
美国科教节目《比尔・奈教科学》主持人
教科学的比尔・奈
Bill Nye the Science Guy.
不好意思  我用新型号替换了你
Sorry, I replaced you with a newer model.
亚瑟・杰弗里斯
Wow, Arthur Jeffries.
见到您真是太荣幸了
It's an honor to meet you.
没有您的铺垫  也不会有我的节目
My show never would have happened without yours.
所以我跟我律师说你是抄袭我
That's what I told my lawyers.
奈先生  你好
Mr. Nye, hello.
被他把你卷进这无谓的纷争里  真是抱歉
I'm sorry he got you involved in this nonsense.
他说是请我来给学生上课的
He said I'd be speaking to a class.
不对  我是说请你来给某人上一课[教训]
No, I said you were teaching someone a lesson.
好了  走吧
Now let's go.
你们在研究什么呢
What are you guys working on?
我们在研制纳米真空管
Oh, uh, we're making nano vacuum tubes.
很有意思嘛
That's interesting.
你从我这里偷的哽还不够吗
Haven't you stolen enough from me?
走开啦  领结男
Back off, bow tie!
各位
Hey, guys...
这一副怎么样
What do you think?
佩妮  做得真漂亮
Wow, Penny, good job.
谢了  在商场买的  4块99
Thanks. Target, $4.99.
我再去倒一杯酒
I'm getting a drink.
你在做什么呢
What are you working on?
帮我妈做一串项链
Oh, I'm making a necklace for my mom.
真孝顺
That's sweet.
最近她和我爸的
Yeah, she and my dad are going through
关系有点紧张
a bit of a rough patch, so
所以我想表示一下让她知道
I wanted to do something to let her know
我挂念着她
I was thinking about her.
他们干嘛吵架呢
What's going on with them?
他们有点小小的沟通不良
They're just having a little trouble communicating.
我爸说我妈的声音
My dad says it's because the sound of my mom's voice
让他想把自己耳朵揪下来
makes him want to tear his ears off
再缝在他的眼睛上
and sew them over his eyes
这样他就永远不用再看见她了
so he never has to look at her again.
嗨
Hi.
-大家好啊  -嗨
- Hey, guys. - Hello.
看看是谁把
Look who's here to put
犹太和珠宝音似
"犹太人"带进"珠宝之夜"了
the "Jew" In "Jewelry Night"!
种族笑话你自己说就没关系是吧
Oh, sure, so it's fine when you say it.
抱歉我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
我顺便去了实验室
I wanted to swing by the lab
把更给力的工具给搬来了
and pick up some even cooler tools for us to use.
我没想到你居然又出现了
I didn't know you were coming again.
上周还挺好玩的
Well, last week was a blast.
再说  我想你们也愿意有个男士陪伴吧
Plus, I thought you might like having a guy here.
其实一点也不好笑
It was not funny.
那你带了什么工具来
So, what tools did you bring?
各种制作珠宝模子的工具
Everything we need to make jewelry molds.
银  坩埚
Here's some silver, a crucible
还有用来融化的乙炔炬
and an acetylene torch to melt it down.
这个看起来有意思
Ooh, that looks like fun.
还是等你先搞定胶水
Maybe you should master glue
再学习玩火吧
before you move on to fire.
好了  谁想先玩啊
Okay, who's up first?
拉杰什  你想再做一副和那项链
Rajesh, do you want to make a bracelet for your mom
搭配的手镯送给你妈吗
to go with the necklace?
不用了
No, thanks.
我也想给我妈做一串项链
I was gonna make a necklace for my mom,
可惜  她胖得脖子都没有
but unfortunately, she doesn't have a neck.
她下巴之下是脂肪  脂肪之下就是脚
She's just chins and fat and feet.
好  我们马上就可以开始了
Okay, we're almost ready to go.
把线连上  就可以开始测试这些管子了
Once we bond the wires, we can test the tubes.
太让人激动了  我觉得
This is so exciting, I-I feel...
就像重新回到75岁一样
like I'm 75 again.
老天爷
Oh, God.
出...什么事了
What... what is it?
谢尔顿发了一张
Sheldon just sent me a picture
他和比尔・奈一起喝冰沙的照片
of him and Bill Nye getting smoothies.
我  我能问个问题吗
Can-can I ask you a question?
当然  问吧
Yeah, sure.
你怎么能忍受谢尔顿这种人啊
W-Why do you put up with Sheldon?
因为我们是朋友呀
Oh, uh, you know, because we're friends.
为什么呀
Why?
-你真喜欢给人出难题  -当然
- Wow, you ask really hard questions. - Yeah.
我知道他总是惹人厌
Look, I-I know he can be aggravating,
但你要知道
but what you have to remember is that
他不是故意的
he's not doing it on purpose.
只是他这人天性如此
It's just how he is.
其实他很忠诚也很可靠
But he's also loyal and trustworthy
我们在一起挺开心的
and we have fun together...
你...你知道自己是在描述一只狗吧
You... you know you're describing a dog.
他的确咬过我一次
He did bite me once.
但他解释说
But in his defense,
我在他进食时突然从背后冒出来  所以
I came up behind him while he was eating, so...
狗都不喜欢那样
Yeah, they-they hate that.
谢尔顿是我遇见过的最聪明的家伙
You know what, Sheldon is the smartest person I have ever met.
他并不是完人  所以才需要我
And he's a little broken and he needs me.
我大概也需要他吧
I guess I need him, too.
为  为什么呢
Why-why is that?
你非得打破沙锅问到底  是吧
Boy, you will not let this go, will you?
我的天
Oh, geez.
又是谢尔顿发来的照片吗
Another photo from Sheldon?
不是  我得去接他一下
No, I have to go pick him up.
比尔・奈把他抛弃在冰沙店了
Bill Nye ditched him at the smoothie place.
大概把他的钱包也顺手偷走了
He probably stole his wallet, too.
如果你们感兴趣的话
You know, if you guys are interested,
有种技术可以让我把你们的一束头发
there's a technique where I can take a lock of your hair,
提炼成碳粉
refine it into carbon dust,
然后用实验室的液压器
and use the hydraulic press at work
把它转变成一颗小小的钻石
to turn it into a tiny little diamond
里面还有你自己的DNA哦
with your DNA in it.
太神奇了吧
Oh, that's amazing!
看到妮妮订婚戒指了吗
Yeah. See Bernie's engagement ring?
原料是我妈背部的体毛
That came right off my mom's back.
他开玩笑的
He's kidding.
真是这样  钻石会大得多
If that were true, it'd be so much bigger.
我叫霍华德
"My name is Howard.
我可以把你的毛发变成钻石
I can make your hair into diamonds.
我妈有病态肥胖症
My mom is morbidly obese.
人人都爱我
Everybody love me."
为啥一股很不爽我的口气
Whoa, where is that coming from?
我告诉你为什么
I'll tell you where it's coming from.
你之前嘲笑我参加闺蜜之夜
All you do is make fun of me for coming to girls' night
现在你又跑来这里毁了大家的好时光
and now you're here ruining it for everyone.
拉杰  淡定
Raj, cool it...
他要给咱们做钻石呢
he's gonna make us hair diamonds.
我怎么毁了你们的好时光
How am I ruining anything?
我只是想帮你把珠宝做得更好
I'm just trying to help you make better jewelry.
但是重点不在珠宝
But this isn't about the jewelry.
而在于在这里
This is about me having a place
我可以敞开心扉  无所不谈
where I can open up about my feelings.
你什么时候开始不能对我敞开心扉谈了
Since when can't you open up with me?
有些话题
There are just some things
我觉得和姑娘们说更自在
that I feel more comfortable sharing with the girls,
因为她们不会嘲笑我
because they won't make fun of me
不会给我取绰号  或是问我
or and call me names, or ask me if my
库萨帕里你的内裤是不是卷在了一起
"Koothrapanties are in a bunch."
意为因为小事就发脾气
兄弟  我那是开玩笑的
Buddy, I was just joking around.
有时候你的玩笑很伤人
Yeah, well, sometimes your jokes hurt.
你说得对
Well, you're right.
我没意识到会让你有这种感受
I didn't realize I was making you feel that way.
你能坦白告诉我真是太勇敢了
It was very brave of you to tell me.
谢谢
Thank you.
对我来说不容易
It wasn't easy.
他们会抢在我和谢尔顿之前先上床
They're gonna have sex before Sheldon and I do,
我就知道
I know it.
亚瑟
Arthur.
你好  谢尔顿
Hi, Sheldon.
真意外在这里看见你
I'm surprised to see you here.
我也意外
Yeah, me, too.
我爬到三楼时
Somewhere around the third floor,
我眼前都开始出现白光了[回光返照]
I began to see a white light.
我去叫莱纳德
I'll get Leonard.
不用  我...
No, no, no, I'm...
我是来找你的
I'm here... I'm here to see you.
如果你想通过我的关系找比尔・奈
If you're hoping to get in touch with Bill Nye,
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
我已经被通知他现在是
I've been informed that he's now
限制令男比尔・奈
Bill Nye the Restraining Order Guy.
不是  我...
No, I'm...
我想  如果不太麻烦的话
I-I was thinking, if it isn't too much trouble,
我希望你给我的论文提提意见
I'd like to get your opinion about my-my paper.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是我的荣幸
It would be an honor.
太好了
Oh. Uh, great.
其实你可以不用给我稿子了
Well, actually, I don't need that.
我已经黑进你的邮箱看过了
I hacked into your e-mail account and read it.
那你觉得如何
And... what did you think?
首先  我觉得
Well, first, I think the fact that
你使用生日作为邮箱密码
you use your birthday as a password
这个错误太丢人
is embarrassing.
多谢提醒
Thank you.
第二
Second, um...
我觉得你的论文极具启发性
I thought your paper was inspired.
你的肯定对我来说意义重大
Oh, well, that... that means a lot to me.
进来喝杯茶好吗
Can I invite you in for tea?
不用了  我真的得...
Uh, no, no. I-I really...
我得走了
I have... I have to run.
亚瑟  你好吗
Hey, Arthur. How are you?
喝一杯也无妨
Well, I guess one cup wouldn't hurt.
兄弟  什么事
Oh, hey, buddy, what's up?
我为自己那天晚上的表现感到内疚
Well, I was feeling bad about how I acted the other night
所以我给你做了个小礼物
so I made you a little something.
这么客气干嘛呀
You didn't have to do that.
很有趣
Well, it was fun.
我运用了你教我们的珠宝制作技艺
I used some of the jewelry techniques you taught us.
这是一个光剑皮带扣
It's a lightsaber belt buckle.
太厉害了  谢谢
Wow, this is so cool, thanks.
好戏在后头
Oh gets better.
更精彩的好戏还在后面  瞧
And that's not even the best part. See?
我也有一个
I have one, too.
你瞧
Check it out.
你可以戴上你的  咱们随时可以来一场
You can wear yours and we can have little sword fights
激情小剑大比拼
whenever we want.
质子教授节目  我心中排名第八的那集是
Yeah, and my eighth favorite episode of Professor Proton
泡腾剂式消化片火箭
was "Alka-Seltzer Rocket."
你说  扑通扑通  嘶嘶嘶嘶
You said, "Plop, plop, fizz, fizz,
精彩的发射来一次
oh, what a blast-off it is."
记得吗  记得这集吗
Remember? Remember that?
记得吗
Remember?
他就是这德行  就是这样
He can't help it. He can't.
他真的没办法
He really can't.
你等着
You wait here.
我去拿些消化片
I'll get some Alka-Seltzer,
我们可以造出火箭
we can build that rocket,
然后朝着比尔・奈家发射
and we can shoot it at Bill Nye's house.
只要我离他超过五百英尺范围就行
As long as I'm not within 500 feet of it.
那么   你...
So, you, uh...
你有没有
you have... you have any...
单身的奶奶或外婆
single grandmothers?
-抱歉  两位都嫁人了  -很好
- Sorry, they're both married. - Good.
婚姻幸福吗
H-Happily?